http://www.floralive.co.uk/en-gb/pages/privacy

- 0 items
(£0.00)
0
Basket
(£0.00)
Privacy Policy
FLORALIVE ("We") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting our store at www.floralive.co.uk you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the "Act"), the data controller is FLORALIVE.INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOUWe may collect and process the following data about you:Information you give us. You may give us information about you by filling in forms on our store at www.floralive.co.uk ("our store") or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number.Information we collect about you. With regard to each of your visits to our store we may automatically collect the following information:Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform;Information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service team.Information we receive from other sources. We may receive information about you from the trusted third parties we are working with (including, for example, business partners, sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services, advertising networks, analytics providers, search information providers and credit reference agencies).USES MADE OF THE INFORMATIONWe use information held about you in the following ways:Information you give to us. We will use this information:To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us and to provide you with the information and services that you request from us;To provide you with information about other services we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about;To provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about goods or services we feel may interest you. If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or negotiations of a sale to you. If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the form on which we collect your data or send your request to assistance@floralive.co.uk.To notify you about changes to our service;To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.Information we collect about you. We will use this information:To administer our site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;To improve our site to ensure that content is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer;To allow you to participate in interactive features of our  service,  when you choose to do so;As part of our efforts to keep our site safe and secure;To measure or understand the effectiveness of advertising we serve to you and others, and to deliver relevant advertising to you;To make suggestions and recommendations to you and other users of our site about goods or services that may interest you or them.Information we receive from other sources. We may combine this information with information you give to us and information we collect about you. We may us this information and the combined information for the purposes set out above (depending on the types of information we receive).DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATIONWe may share your information with selected third parties including:Business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we enter into with them or you.Analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimisation of our site.Credit reference agencies for the purpose of assessing your credit score where this is a condition of us entering into a contract with you.We may disclose your personal information to third parties:In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.If FLORALIVE or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions of service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of FLORALIVE, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATAThe data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.Our card payment facility is provided by PayPal who are fully compliant with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards.  Any payment transactions carried out through our website or over the phone will be encrypted. We do not hold or process any payment card details on our servers. This information is processed by PayPal on their secure servers. To view a copy of PayPal's privacy policy for the United Kingdom please copy and paste the following link into your web browser: https://www.paypal.com/uk/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-prev We may also store manual copies of your personal information (but not your payment card information) in a secure facility where access is restricted.Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.YOUR RIGHTSYou have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at assistance@floralive.co.uk.Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.ACCESS TO INFORMATIONThe Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10.00 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYAny changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.CONTACTQuestions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to assistance@floralive.co.uk.Page last updated: 18/11/18
Carnivorous Plants - Peat-Free
We grow and supply peat-free cultivated Carnivorous Plants suitable for beginners and specialists alike.Based in the U.K., we are pioneers in the formulation and use of peat-free growing media for Carnivorous Plants. We also offer our acclaimed THRIVE™ Carnivorous Plant Compost along with a range of top-quality growing accessories.
We Accept
Connect With Us
Twitter
Sign Up For Our Newsletter
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Returns Policy
Disclaimer of Liability
